[{"answer": "I really don't think so.", "docId": "130403pmt", "aSentId": 26, "question": "P.J. Crowley, are we heading to any kind of nuclear conflict with North Korea here?", "qSentId": 25}, {"answer": "I think we need to be careful there.", "docId": "130403pmt", "aSentId": 35, "question": "At what point should the United States consider some kind of military attack, albeit from a defensive standpoint if we can't put up with these saber rattling threats any longer?", "qSentId": 34}, {"answer": "I think -- I think -- Piers, you're exactly right.", "docId": "130403pmt", "aSentId": 48, "question": "Should China be doing more to get North Korea to put a cork on it, to put it bluntly?", "qSentId": 47}, {"answer": "ROWLEY: Well, they have a nuclear capability.", "docId": "130403pmt", "aSentId": 57, "question": "How far could they reach?", "qSentId": 56}, {"answer": "I did retract is because after rereading it and then, you know, hearing from you and other people say, maybe it was a bit crass to use that word.", "docId": "130403pmt", "aSentId": 110, "question": "Why did you retract it?", "qSentId": 109}, {"answer": "I have friends together 40 years.", "docId": "130403pmt", "aSentId": 127, "question": "ORGAN: Do you?", "qSentId": 126}, {"answer": "You are linking --", "docId": "130403pmt", "aSentId": 150, "question": "Do you agree to that?", "qSentId": 149}, {"answer": "Let me tell you what I don't agree with.", "docId": "130403pmt", "aSentId": 152, "question": "Do you agree to that?", "qSentId": 151}, {"answer": "But it's interesting.", "docId": "130403pmt", "aSentId": 159, "question": "Do you understand why gay people -- why gay people find that particularly offensive?", "qSentId": 158}, {"answer": "Let me talk about redefinition of marriage.", "docId": "130403pmt", "aSentId": 194, "question": "Where does it stop?", "qSentId": 193}, {"answer": "You've raised a good point.", "docId": "130403pmt", "aSentId": 196, "question": "Where does it stop?", "qSentId": 195}, {"answer": "Those are laws that were made by man.", "docId": "130403pmt", "aSentId": 210, "question": "What is your answer to that?", "qSentId": 209}, {"answer": "I don't think it's a perfectly fine alternative.", "docId": "130403pmt", "aSentId": 242, "question": "You said ultimately it's about changing the culture of the country, it inevitably lead to teaching our public school kids that gay marriage is a perfectly fine alternative and no different -- why shouldn't they be taught that gay marriage is a perfectly fine alternative?", "qSentId": 241}, {"answer": "Same-sex marriage.", "docId": "130403pmt", "aSentId": 247, "question": "Hmm?", "qSentId": 246}, {"answer": "I'm not going to get into if it's a crime against nature, whatever.", "docId": "130403pmt", "aSentId": 249, "question": "Is it a crime against nature?", "qSentId": 248}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "130403pmt", "aSentId": 298, "question": "Pretty shocking stuff from Michael Reagan, wasn't it?", "qSentId": 297}, {"answer": "Well, I don't know.", "docId": "130403pmt", "aSentId": 381, "question": "It just annoys people, doesn't it?", "qSentId": 380}, {"answer": "No, sir, not at all.", "docId": "130403pmt", "aSentId": 411, "question": "So it's not as bad as we think, this guy?", "qSentId": 410}, {"answer": "Yes, it is.", "docId": "130403pmt", "aSentId": 425, "question": "I mean, this is unusual behavior, even by sporting coach standards, isn't it?", "qSentId": 424}, {"answer": "Yes, sir.", "docId": "130403pmt", "aSentId": 444, "question": "ORGAN: I mean did -- did other players feel that he went too far?", "qSentId": 443}, {"answer": "You know, he would get into, you know, heated argument.", "docId": "130403pmt", "aSentId": 448, "question": "And how would he react if anyone tried to stand up to him?", "qSentId": 447}, {"answer": "No, sir, not at all.", "docId": "130403pmt", "aSentId": 456, "question": "Was he ever homophobic when you were playing in terms of the way he spoke to players and was he ever racist?", "qSentId": 455}, {"answer": "Yes, he did.", "docId": "130403pmt", "aSentId": 462, "question": "Did he motivate you?", "qSentId": 461}, {"answer": "Well, I felt that he was -- he was viewed in a -- in a wrong manner.", "docId": "130403pmt", "aSentId": 486, "question": "Why not?", "qSentId": 485}, {"answer": "Well, even if he deviated from the standard of care, he didn't cause the death of Michael Jackson because on the night Michael Jackson died, he was not on a propofol drip.", "docId": "130403pmt", "aSentId": 500, "question": "Valerie?", "qSentId": 499}, {"answer": "Absolutely.", "docId": "130403pmt", "aSentId": 507, "question": "Did you read the toxicology?", "qSentId": 506}, {"answer": "That's correct.", "docId": "130403pmt", "aSentId": 511, "question": "He had propofol in every single of the eight specimens, OK?", "qSentId": 510}, {"answer": "First of all, I'd like to point out that Conrad Murray never received a dime for caring for Michael Jackson.", "docId": "130403pmt", "aSentId": 567, "question": "What was expected of Conrad Murray, and is it true that it was AEG paying Conrad Murray directly, not Michael Jackson?", "qSentId": 566}, {"answer": "But that becomes an issue of litigation between Conrad Murray and AEG, I guess.", "docId": "130403pmt", "aSentId": 579, "question": "Isn't a doctor paid -- if you render services for two months, aren't you paid for those services if your patient dies and suddenly you aren't -- you don't get paid for the two months that you took care of a patient?", "qSentId": 578}, {"answer": "Very significant.", "docId": "130403pmt", "aSentId": 597, "question": "Well, Tom, I mean -- Tom, from a legal point of view, that e- mail is going to be pretty significant, isn't it?", "qSentId": 596}, {"answer": "And he's a drummer.", "docId": "130403pmt", "aSentId": 658, "question": "And you'd lost your left leg and nearly died?", "qSentId": 657}, {"answer": "I was behind him 10 feet.", "docId": "130403pmt", "aSentId": 683, "question": "When this accident happened, did you both feel that this could be it, that you were going to die?", "qSentId": 682}, {"answer": "The leg is wonderful.", "docId": "130403pmt", "aSentId": 755, "question": "How is the leg?", "qSentId": 754}, {"answer": "The leg is a -- every hour it feels like, you know, it's Christmas Day to me right now.", "docId": "130403pmt", "aSentId": 759, "question": "$6 million man?", "qSentId": 758}]